# **Pushan** Pore

### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

I am currently working as a Junior Data Engineer at Capgemini, where I have been working for the past 2 years. With my 2 years of experience in data management and CMDB Management, I am now seeking a more data-focused role. I am proficient in SQL, Python and Excel with a keen interest in Azure data services such as Azure Data Factory and Azure Storage Services. I am 2 X Azure Certified.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### <u>Capgemini Technology Services India</u> SR. ANALYST

Jul 2024 - Present

SQL script development using PostgreSQL | Cleaning up crude Data using Python and Excel | Data Visualization using Power BI |CMDB Manager

# Capgemini Technology Services India

### **ANALYST**

Sept 2022 - Jul 2024

CMDB Manager | Supporting NL clients to manage their repository of Physical and virtual assets with maximum data accuracy | Expertise in Data Analysis with excel and Python

#### CodeDrills

#### INTERNSHIP

May 2022 - Sept 2022

SQL and MCQ problem setter for hiring assessments and interviews.

## Capgemini Technology Services India

### **INTERNSHIP**

Jan 2022 – Apr 2022

Full stack Engineer Intern | Spring Boot, Angular, PostgreSQL

### CONTACT

Mail: pushan.pore.work@gmail.com

Phone: (+91) 9073775628 Location: Mumbai / Kolkata Current Address: Navi Mumbai,

Maharashtra

### **EDUCATION**

B. Tech, Computer Science and Engineering GPA: 8.73 / 10 2018 - 2022

### **SKILLS**

- Python (Pandas, Numpy)
- SQL(Expertise in Working With Procedural Logic)
- Excel
- Power BI
- ServiceNow (CSA Certified)
- CMDB Management

### **SOCIAL LINKS**

• Linked-In:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/pushan-pore-1401/

Website : Portfolio

CodeChef:

https://www.codechef.com/users/pushan014

CodeForces:

https://codeforces.com/pr ofile/pushan.pore

### CERTIFICATION

- Microsoft Azure DP-203
- Microsoft Azure DP-900
- ServiceNow CSA